

Rhaony Moura Ferraz

Phone: (19) 99448-2889

WhatsApp: +353 83 875 2770

E-mail: rhaonyferraz@hotmail.com.br



Profile: https://rhaonyferraz.github.io/html-css/ GitHub: https://github.com/RhaonyFerraz

Address: 1359 Luiz Antônio Pires Itobi SP / Brazil







Profile

Full Stack with focus on complex processes and solutions development, developing tools and managing projects globally, providing technical and commercial solutions for the best customer experience.

Key strengths: teamwork, clear thinker, pro-activity, presentation skills, Excellent communication skills

Employment History

Front end developer/Marcelo Pasqua Ltda 2020-2022 http://marcelopasqua.com/

- Innovation management.
- Weekly meetings with investors.
- Development of new customers.
- Implementation of new cybersecurity systems.
- Token creation. https://www.cryptorig.com.br/
- Website development/web2.0/3.0.

Full stack, Bridge Trade -Ireland. 2018 - 2021 https://bridgetrade.biz/

- Project flow management.
- Preparation of presentations for investors.
- Review of cybersecurity and new technologies;
- Report analysis.

Technology analyst, Textil União Ltda. 2015 - 2017 http://textiluniao.ind.br/

- Hardware and software management.
- Implementation of new systems.
- Weekly meetings with the board/customers

Technology analyst, Ferraz Ltda 2012 - 2014 https://.embreagemferraz.com.br/

- Weekly meetings with the board;
- Implementation of new systems.



Educational Background

University graduate

University UNIVESP 2021 (studying)
Computer Engineering.
Infinity Business School (Ireland) 2017/19
Advanced English

Specialization and certification

Cybersecurity -Cisco-Meta Verse-Cloud, Business Sales, computig-Gravity Stecks-NFT Developer-Blockchain Developer-Mikro tik-Vr Developer-Solidity-JavaScrit-Html-Css-Mine Coins-Game Engineering -Game Design-Unity 3D.

Academic Project

University Unifeg 2014-2017 Project Coordination-Baja Academic merit. https://.youtube.com/watch? v=HtjnH3FAjN0&t=59s

Skills

- Fluent English
- Spanish intermediary
- Systems specialist.
- Skill with technologies.
- Communication skill.
- Commercial skills.

References

Marcelo Pasqua CEO- +55 11 98616-5565 Tristan M:CEO BridgeTrade +353 85 744-1805 Dr: Reginaldo Arthus - Unifeg +55 35 3551-5267 Gilmar M: CEO Textil União+55 35 9121-5415 Renan F: Embreagens Ferraz+55 35 8812-9405